Inventory of the Paul N. McCloskey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington, D.C. office (Box 78)
  - Miscellany. United Nations Peace through Law research materials
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 94)
    - "K--Executive" to "N--Foreign affairs--Mideast,", 1970
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 95)
    - FEC (Federal Elections Commission) reports re-elect, 1977-1980
    - Californians for McCloskey FEC reports, 1981
    - Files on Wilson, Hayakawa, Bruinsma, Cornan, Goldwater, Brown FEC
    - "Political--Advisory Committees" to "Political--Supporters,", 1969 (Box 96)
    - Senate campaign notebooks and FEC reports, 1982 (Box 97)
    - Letters and mailing lists
  - Miscellany. Nelson Rockefeller investigation materials, 1974 (Box 98)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file. Fishing streams files, 1972 (Box 99)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 100)
    - "B--Energy" to "D--Defense--Spending,", 1974
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1974 (Box 101)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 102)
    - "R--Requests--Agriculture yearbooks" to "S--Invitations--South Vietnam students,", 1974
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file. H.R. 9998 - H.R. 17360 (with gaps), and various resolutions, etc., 1973-1974 (Box 103)
  - Miscellany
    - McCloskey legislation
    - "Dear Colleagues" files, 1973
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 104)
    - "A--District" to "B--Energy--Oil industry,", 1974
    - "Q--Academies" to "Q--Academies--Air Force--1970 nominated,", 1970-1975. (Box 105)
      Includes some general files, 1970-1975
    - "M--DURAs,", 1974. (Box 106)
      Form letters from "G:Impeachment" to "P:Political," 1974. DURAs refers to the computerized form letter response system
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file. H.R. 4 - H.R. 9943 (with gaps), and various resolutions, etc., 1973 (Box 107)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 108)
    - "Q--Academies,", 1970-1974
    - "G--Government--Reform" to "H--HEW (Housing, Education and Welfare)--FDA (Food and Drug Administration),", 1974 (Box 109)
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1974 (Box 110)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 111)
    - "R--Office--Thanks sent June/July" to "R--Office--Recommendations,", 1974
    - "S--Invitations--Out of town reject" to "S--Invitations--Out of town accept,", 1974 (Box 112)
    - "D--Defense--Veterans" to "E--Economy--Labor and strikes,", 1974 (Box 113)
    - "J--Environment" to "J--Environment--New Melones,", 1974 (Box 114)
    - "J--Environment--Natural Resources Defense Council" to "P--Political--Gary Gillmore,", 1974 (Box 115)
    - "R--Office--Thanks sent" to "X--Casework--Private Kerry N. Mock,", 1974 (Box 116)
    - "M--DURAs.", 1974. (Box 117)
      Form letters from "A:District" to "H:HEW (Housing, Education and Welfare)." DURAs refers to the computerized form letter response system
    - "H--HEW (Health, Education and Welfare)--Health insurance" to "I--Transportation--Railroads,", 1974 (Box 118)
    - "G--Government" to "G--Government--Postal Service,", 1974 (Box 119)
    - "N--Names--Frank and Margo Blair" to "N--Names--Louis Wolfson,", 1974 (Box 120)
    - "S--Invitations--Out of town and district office speaking schedules,", 1974
    - P--Political--Campaigning for others" to "P--Political--Primary election '74,", 1974 (Box 121)
    - "E--Economy--OSHA (Occupational Safety and Health Administration)" to "F--Foreign affairs--Soviet Jews,", 1974 (Box 122)
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 123)
    - Briefing books
      - Rhode Island, North Carolina, Wisconsin, Massachusetts, Oregon, 1971
      - North Carolina Student Legislature, 1972
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 124)
    - "G--Government" to "I--Transportation--Space,", 1972
  - Committee on Government Operations file. Foreign Operations and Government Information Subcommittee, 1972 (Box 125)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file
    - Conservation and Natural Resources Subcommittee, 1972
    - Ocean Subcommittee, 1972
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 126)
    - Presidential campaign state material, 1971
    - Presidential campaign New Hampshire press releases, 1971 (Box 127)
  - Staff members' files--J. Wilson (Box 128)
    - Oregon conservation issues
    - Tocks Island Reservoir
    - Potomac River, Rogue River
    - Redwood National Park
    - Colorado River Basin project
    - San Francisco Bay
    - Solid waste
    - 1-3 Negative income tax/Guaranteed annual income, 1970
    - Nutrition
    - Whitten amendments, 1969-1970
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 129)
    - "U--Political--Finances, presidential," to "U--Political--Volunteer groups (Republican),", 1972
    - "S--Invitations accepted" to "S--Invitations in district,", 1973 (Box 130)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file. Special Subcommittee on Maritime Education and Training, 1972 (Box 131)
  - Miscellany
    - 8-66 Club, 1972
    - Wednesday Club, 1972
    - Peace Alert USA, 1972
    - Nixon environmental message, 1971-1972
    - Presidential press releases, 1972
    - Republican task force subcommittee on population growth, 1972
    - Members of Congress for Peace through Law, 1972
    - United Nations conference on the human environment, 1972
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 132)
    - Briefing books
      - New Mexico official returns (primary and general election), 1970
      - Colorado, New Hampshire, Oregon, 1971
    - Clippings--North Carolina, 1971
  - Staff members' files--J. Wilson (Box 133)
    - Supreme Court Rehnquist nomination
    - National Industrial Pollution Control Council, 1972
    - Busing, 1971
    - Revenue sharing, 1972
    - Ocean mammals, 1972
    - California--General
    - Indians
    - Lake Tahoe
    - Maritime Academy of California
    - Morongo Basin power lines
    - Peripheral canal
    - San Rafael Independent Journal strike (Box 133)
    - Welfare reform
    - San Mateo County
    - Southern crossing
    - Beach erosion
    - Navy--San Bruno
    - Pescadero Dam
    - Raker Act
    - San Francisco Bay Area marshlands
    - Housing
    - Flower growers
    - Desegregation
    - Veteran's benefits
    - Nixon messages to Congress, 1972
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 134)
    - Briefing books. New Hampshire, California, Wisconsin, 1971
    - New Mexico election returns, (1911-1969)
    - Clippings concerning McCloskey campaigns, 1971-1972
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 135)
    - "U--Political--Presidential campaign,", 1971
    - "J--Environment" to "P--Publications-- Congressional Record,", 1972 (Box 136)
  - Letters sent (pink copies). Dr - Z, 1973 (Box 137)
  - Campaign/Political file. Presidential state campaign materials, 1971 (Box 138)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 139)
    - "O--Activities--Requests--Media" to "U--Political--Finances, congressional,", 1972
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 140)
    - Campaign binder, 1971
    - Clipping binders, 1971
    - State briefing books, 1971
    - Clippings, 1971 (Box 141)
    - State briefing books for Massachusetts and New Hampshire, 1971
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 142)
    - "N--Names--Butler, Lewis" to "S--Invitations--Washington--Regretted Jan-March,", 1972
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1971 (Box 143)
  - Staff members' files--J. Wilson (Box 144)
    - Environmental education
    - Nixon on environment
    - California land conservation
    - Public Land Law Review Commission
    - Water resources management
    - McCloskey on land use reform
    - Legal Services Corporation, 1971
    - Pesticide bill, 1971
    - Consumer Protection Act, 1971
    - Longshoremen strike, 1971
    - Ocean dumping legislation, 1971
    - Food stamps, 1971
    - Health insurance, 1971
    - Medicare, 1971
    - School prayer, 1971
    - Water pollution control bill, 1971
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 145)
    - "U--Political--Recess letter,", 1973
  - Miscellany. Form letter to 17th Congressional District lawyers, 1973
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 146)
    - "G--Government--Office of presidential secretary" to "G--Government--Tax reform,", 1973
    - "I--Transportation--Highways" to "J--Environment--Pipelines,", 1973 (Box 147)
    - "M--DURAs,", 1973. (Box 148)
      Form letters from "A:17th District" to "J:Environment." DURAs refers to the computerized form letter response system
  - Letters sent (pink copies) (Box 149)
    - A - Z, 1973 January
    - A - Dq, 1973 July - December
  - Campaign/Political file. Presidential campaign material, 1971-1972 (Box 150)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 151)
    - "R--Office--Administrative files,", 1974
    - "T--PNM (P. N. McCloskey) personal" to "T--PNM personal--1974 memberships,"
  - Subject file (no file codes, alphabetical by subject). "Academies,", 1968-1969 (Box 152)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "T--PNM (P. N. McCloskey) personal--Book general,", 1971-1972
    - "T--PNM personal--Financial matters,", 1972
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 153)
    - Card file of 1972 key campaign contacts
    - Statement of contributions and expenses for election as representative in Congress, 1970 December 7
    - Deposits made--McCloskey for Congress, 1968
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 154)
    - "F--Foreign affairs--War (January-March)" to "G--Government--Office of President (August-September),", 1973
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 155)
    - Fundraising, 1970-1974 (bulk 1972)
    - Appearances
    - Lobbyists
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 156)
    - "J--Environment--Indians" to "O--Activities--Thanks received,", 1973
    - "M--DURAs,", 1972. (Box 157)
      Form letters from "D:Defense" to "L:Law enforcement." DURAs refers to computerized form letter response system
    - "U--Political,", 1972
  - Miscellany
    - Tax questionnaire project, 1972 May
    - Thanks sent
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 158)
    - "D--Defense" to "E--Economy--Press freedom,", 1973
    - "O--Activities--Shockley" to "U--Political--Supporters,", 1973 (Box 159)
    - "A--Grants and contracts" to "F--Foreign affairs--United Nations,", 1972 (Box 160)
    - "N--Names--Members of Congress," to "T--PNM (P. N. McCloskey) personal,", 1973 (Box 161)
  - Campaign/Political file. Finances and letters, 1968-1972 (Box 162)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 163)
    - "A--17th District" to "C--California--State water plan,", 1973
    - "N--Names--Chandler, Tertius and Margo" to "N--Names--Wells, Albert,", 1973 (Box 164)
    - "R--Office,", 1973
  - Campaign/Political file. Campaign materials, 1968-1972 (Box 165)
  - Miscellany. Special projects--Electric car, 1974
  - Campaign/Political file. Presidential campaign finance records, 1972 (Box 166)
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1974 (Box 167)
  - Staff members' files (Box 168)
    - Trails and bicycle trails, 1974
    - Reagan tax initiative, 1974
    - Railroads, 1974
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 169)
    - Offshore ports, 1973
    - Fisheries and wildlife conservation, 1973
    - H. Con. Res. 157, 1973
    - Endangered species, 1973
    - Deepwater ports, 1973
  - Printed matter. "Public Hearings of the Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities of the U.S. Senate" (93/1), 1973-1974. (Box 170)
    29 volumes including hearings, appendix, final report, index
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file. Law of the Sea and Deep Sea Bed Mining Act, 1978. (Box 171)
    Includes files on international resources and post-Geneva briefings
  - Staff members' files--Jack Sands (Box 172)
    - Cargo preference, 1977
    - Maritime regulatory reform legislation, 1981-1982
    - Campaign contributions, 1978
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 173)
    - Cargo preference, bulk 1977
  - Miscellany. Point of Americas condo apartments--Corps of Engineers--Erosion problem, 1981-1982
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 174)
    - Jones Act/Forest products, 1981
    - Third flag
    - Bruja Mar waiver, H.R. 7114
    - Pax on foreign flag, H.R. 1288
    - Nuclear ship development, H.R. 13505
    - Endangered species
    - Fisheries--200 mile bill, H.R. 200, 1974
    - Fisheries development, H.R. 7039, 1980
    - Coastal zone management, H.R. 6979, 1980-1981 (Box 175)
    - Barrier islands
    - Outer Continental Shelf Lands Act
    - Ocean dumping, 1982
    - Scuttle nuclear submarines
    - Leasing/Oil spill liability
  - Staff members' files--Ron Losch (Box 176)
    - Law of the sea, 1970s-1982
  - Printed matter (Box 177)
    - "Hearings and Report of the Foreign Operations and Government Information Subcommittee, Committee on Government Operations," volume 1 (93rd Congress), 1973-1974
    - "Hearings and Report of the Conservation and Natural Resources Subcommittee, Committee on Government Operations," (93rd Congress), volumes 1, 2, 4, 5, 1973-1974
    - "House Rules and Manual," 92nd Congress, 93rd Congress
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file. H.R. 46 TO H.R. 13261 (with gaps), and various resolutions, etc., 1971-1972. (Box 178)
    Copies of bills only
  - Miscellany (Box 179)
    - House resolutions, etc., 1971-1972
    - McCloskey "Dear Colleague" letters, 1971-1972
    - Legislative analysis, 92nd Congress, 1st session
    - D.S.G. analysis, 92nd Congress, 1st session/Weekly legislative calendar
    - Pollution initiative
    - Skyline Parkway, 1968-1970
    - SST (Supersonic Transport), 1969-1971
    - Lockheed, 1971
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 180)
    - Campaign finance records, 1972
    - Bank statements and checkbooks
    - Presidential campaign records (Box 181)
      - Fundraising--Lists of contributors, 1971-1972
      - Campaign strategy, 1972 (Box 182)
      - Volunteers, 1972
      - Mailing lists on cards (Box 183)
  - Miscellany. Colma Creek project, 1969-1971
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 184)
    - Presidential campaign records
      - Mailing lists on cards
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 185)
    - "H--HEW (Health, Education and Welfare)--Aid to private schools" to "I--Transportation--Hijacking,", 1973
    - "U--Political--Republican leadership letters" to "X--Casework,", 1973 (Box 186)
    - "E--Economy--Pensions" to "F--Foreign affairs--United Nations,", 1973 (Box 187)
  - Campaign/Political file, 1978-1982 (bulk 1980) (Box 188)
    - Republican Party
    - 1980 Congressional campaign
    - Requests for endorsements
    - Ron Diridon
    - Anti-McCloskey
    - Campaigning for others
    - NRCC open seats to watch
    - Wednesday Group
    - 1980 Congressional campaign (Box 189)
    - Questionnaires
    - President Reagan correspondence
    - Reagan endorsement of McCloskey
    - John Anderson
    - McCloskey presidency?
    - Fundraising
    - PAC information
    - Kirsten Olsen
    - Senate possibility 1979 for 1982
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 190)
    - "O--Office" to "T--PNM (P. N. McCloskey)--Memberships,", 1975
    - "C--California--Public Health Service Hospital San Francisco,", 1973 (Box 191)
  - Miscellany
    - Tussock moth DDT
    - Equal employment opportunity enforcement
    - New Melones Dam, 1973
    - International coffee agreement, 1971
    - Child support, 1974
    - Amnesty, 1974
    - Soft drink industry
    - Court decisions on busing
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1974 (Box 192)
    - Report on federal expenditures on presidential properties
    - Computers--Information technology
    - International debt collection
    - Polygraph technology
    - Telephone monitoring and other surveillance practices of the federal government
    - Security classification legislation
  - Letters sent (pink copies). Ph - Z, 1975 January - June (Box 193)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 194)
    - "S--Invitations--In district accept (January-June)" to "S--Invitations--Out of town reject (July-December),", 1975
  - Miscellany (Box 195)
    - Boston U.S. Public Health Service Hospital, 1971
    - Water resources
    - Proposal for national land-use commission by McCloskey in Michigan Law Review, 1970
    - Water pollution, 1971
    - Bureau of Land Management manual on planning system for multiple land use decisions, 1969
    - McCloskey planning and scheduling correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 196)
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file. H.R. 13728 - H.R. 16683 (with gaps), various resolutions, etc. (92nd Congress), 1971-1972
  - Miscellany (Box 197)
    - Unemployment insurance--Farm workers
    - Rockefeller Commission report
    - Land use
    - Family planning testimony
    - Campaign reform status
    - My Lai
    - NAACP--Legal Defense Fund speech
    - State Department authority conference report
    - Palo Alto landfill application--Corps of Engineers
    - San Mateo legal services grant renewal controversy, 1973
    - OEO (Office of Equal Opportunity)/Legal services, 1973
    - Stride
    - EPA (Environmental Protection Agency) reimbursement grant regulations, 1973
    - Sequoia Union School District
  - Printed matter. Hearings, reports, committee prints of various subcommittees of the Government Operations Committee (90th Congress), 1967-1968 (Box 198)
  - Miscellany (Box 199)
    - Impeachment letters received with some form replies, 1974
    - Reapportionment, 1973 (Box 200)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1974 (Box 201)
    - Intermodal
    - London conference
    - Import restrictions to discourage whaling violations, H.R. 15039
    - Ocean dumping
    - Marine mammals
    - Oil imports hearings
    - Merchant Marine Subcommittee
    - Oceanography Subcommittee
    - Intercoastal Shipping Act
    - Liner conference briefing
    - Cargo preference
    - Fishing streams
  - Miscellany
    - Members of Congress for Peace through Law, 1974
    - Ripon Society, 1974
    - Wednesday Club, 1974
    - Task Force on Anticompetitive Practices and Monopolistic Powers, 1974
    - Department of Defense, 1973
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "T--PNM (P. N. McCloskey) Personal--Department of Defense letters,", 1971
  - Committee on Government Operations file (Box 202)
    - Freedom of Information, 1974
    - Foreign operations and government information, 1974
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file
    - General, 1974
    - Wildlife Coordination Act
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 203)
    - "E--Economy--Banking" to "E--Economy--Housing,", 1975
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file. Tuna/ Porpoise, 1976 (Box 204)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 205)
    - "X--Casework--Nieto" to "X--Casework--White,", 1975
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1973 (Box 206)
    - General
    - Foreign operations and government information
    - Federal Energy Administration, H.R. 11793
    - Freedom of Information data
    - Foreign operations hearings--testimonies and background
  - Miscellany. "Dear Colleague" letters, 1973
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1975 (Box 207)
    - Whithead testimony
    - FOGI--Nonmilitary assistance in Southeast Asia
    - FOGI--Laos hearings
    - CIA (Central Intelligence Agency) investigation
    - Subpoena power
    - Mary C. Lawton testimony
    - FOGI report: Security classification
    - Freedom of information
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file
    - Conservation and natural resources
    - Stream channelization
  - Miscellany
    - Effect of coal mining on Corps
    - Control of pollution from animal feedlots
    - U.S. assistance programs in Vietnam
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 208)
    - H--HEW (Health, Education and Welfare)--Handicapped" to "L--Law enforcement--Pornography,", 1975
    - "E--Economy--IRS (Internal Revenue Service) to "F--Foreign affairs--Europe,", 1975 (Box 209)
    - "G--Government--Postal Service,", 1975
  - Printed matter (Box 210)
    - Statement of information: Hearings before the Committee on the Judiciary, House of Representatives (93-2) regarding whether sufficient grounds exist to impeach Richard M. Nixon, 15 volumes, 1975
    - Hearings, appendix, index, of the Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities of the U.S. Senate (93d Cong.) covering Watergate investigation, milk fund investigation, Hughes-Rebozo investigation, campaign financing, campaign practices, 23 volumes, 1974 (Box 211)
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 212)
    - Primary McCloskey notebook, 1972
    - Notebook, 1970
    - Primary and general notebook, 1970
    - Campaign letters, 1972
    - Surveys notebook, 1968
    - Primary and general notebook, 1968
    - The complete presidential candidate (issues) notebook, 1972 (Box 213)
    - Lists of contacts, 1972
    - State election laws and ballots, etc., 1972
    - Republican convention delegates, 1972
    - New Mexico briefing book, 1972
  - Miscellany. Names and addresses on scriptomatic cards, undated (Box 214)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 215)
    - "M--DURAs,", 1975
    - "V--Press,", 1975
    - "F--Foreign affairs--Food" to "G--Government--Office of the President,", 1975 (Box 216)
    - "C--California" to "E--Economy--Budget,", 1975 (Box 217)
  - Government Operations Committee file, 1975-1976 (Box 218)
    - Full committee meetings
    - Information and Individual Rights Subcommittee
    - Conservation, Energy and Natural Resources Subcommittee
    - Other subcommittees
    - Bureau of Reclamation indexing procedures
    - FBI recordkeeping
    - Discriminatory assignment policies of federal agencies
    - Cable interception and telephone monitoring
    - J. Edgar Hoover's FBI (Federal Bureau of Investigation) files
    - International Women's Year
    - Prosecution of CIA (Central Intelligence Agency) criminal violations
    - Notice of illegal surveillance
    - Teton Dam
    - National Park Service
    - Oil shale
    - Pesticide control
    - Foster City
    - Solid waste management
    - Energy policy oversight
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 219)
    - "X--Casework--Ampex" to "X--Casework--Murcock Machine Company,", 1975
    - "L--Law enforcement--Press" to "R--Requests--Congressional documents,", 1975 (Box 220)
  - Miscellany. Names and addresses on scriptomatic cards, undated (Box 221)
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Rq, 1975 July to December (Box 222)
  - Miscellany (Box 223)
    - District press book, 1970-1971
    - Clippings, 1968
    - Draft and notes for book, 1971
    - Land use policy (Box 224)
    - Open spaces
    - Outdoor recreation
    - Property tax
    - Open space element of the Palo Alto general plan
    - Report of the Public Land Law Review Commission
    - Alternative GOP (Republican) platform
  - Printed matter. Calendar, House bills, reports, etc., of the Committee on Government Operations (90th Congress), 3 volumes, 1967-1968 (Box 225)
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Pg, 1975 January - June (Box 226)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 227)
    - "H--HEW (Health, Education and Welfare)--Youth" to "J--Environment--Land use,", 1975
  - Letters sent (pink copies). Rs - Z, 1975 July -December (Box 228)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 229)
    - "G--Government--Postal Service" to "H--HEW (Health, Education and Welfare),", 1975
    - "R--Requests--Pages" to "R--Requests--Visitors,", 1975 (Box 230)
    - "F--Foreign affairs--Southeast Asia,", 1975 January - May (Box 231)
  - Miscellany. U.S. Public Health Service hospital conversion study, 1971. (Box 232)
    Includes minutes, reports, summaries, etc., and proposals for Boston, Staten Island, Baltimore, Norfolk, New Orleans, Galveston, San Francisco, Seattle
  - Printed matter. Department of State "Background Notes" on various countries, 1971-1972
  - Miscellany. To establish an agency for consumer protection, H.R. 7575, 1975-1976 (Box 233)
  - Select Committee on Missing Persons in Southeast Asia file, 1976 (Box 234)
  - Miscellany, 1976-1977 (Box 235)
    - Contact people
    - Energy
    - Coal slurry pipelines
    - Communications
    - Budget act and zero-based budget